Chapter 13
Benjamin and I went into the office,
plugged in the computer, and started
working right away. We had to
hurry, really hurry. I started writing
furiously while Benjamin
rearranged his notes, listed the
photographs and drawings. Five minutes
after we arrived, Tea called
to ask if we were finished. I kept quiet about
everything I thought because I'm
a well-behaved mouse. Ten minutes
later,
Trapita called to recommend that I
put her photo in the book. I kept quiet about
everything I thought because I'm a
well-behaved mouse. Fifteen minutes later,
Tenebrosa called to ask me if she
should paint her nails purple for the party
or black. I kept quiet about
everything I thought because I'm a
well-behaved mouse.
20 minutes later Pina called to
ask if she could
prepare mummy eyeballs in
pesto for our menu instead of mummified bat balls.
I kept quiet about everything I thought
because I'm a well-behaved mouse. 25
minutes later Pink called to
inform me that I had captivated  a
dark one but was famous for its
tremendous scenes of jealousy I kept everything I
thought to myself because I'm a well-
behaved mouse 30 minutes later Tea called me
to ask if I was done this
time even though I'm a well-behaved mouse I didn't
keep everything I thought to myself offended she
hung up the receiver on my face
Benjamin and I decided to pick up the
phone and from that moment on
we worked calmly work work
work until I
typed the last sentence and I breathed a
sigh of relief at that moment Tea came in and
took my paws off the
keys stop that's enough whatever you've
written is written
Benjamin gave me a kiss on the tip of my
whiskers man you're great fantastic
super mouse and ccoo I smiled under my
whiskers I didn't think I'd be able to
write a book so quickly now
we can finally relax
chapter 14 finally the night
of October 31st arrived
Pina had insisted on cooking at
my grandfather's house who has a huge
and very complete kitchen luckily my grandfather
was abroad so we had
his kitchen at our  position planted
in front of the stove pina wielded the
silver rolling pin on which were
engraved her initials a gift from my
grandfather while he shouted orders
left and right to his assistants you
get me that saucepan if I tell you to
you hake snout and you each cheese
pass me that frying pan quickly you idiot
what are you doing you're asleep move your
joint tail I sleep with my cheese that
betrayal move as soon as she finished
cooking at eight we transported the
food to the crypt of tenebrosa
9 the guests began to arrive I saw
a guy dressed as a tombstone
another decided to be funereal another painted with
fluorescent varnish and naturally
witches wizards vampires
mummies specters
ghosts cats werewolves the orchestra
began to play the romantic
bat waltz and everyone came out to dance
just at that moment I heard someone poor
me shouting at me jeronimo
jeronimo
tenebrosa grabbed me by the leg and
dragged me in a wild waltz
while I  she languidly murmured in my
ear, "My little cheese, I've missed you."
To change the subject, I directed her
toward the buffet where Pina was preparing the menu. I
tried a spoonful
of delicious sewer worms. Next to
me, I
saw Tenebrosa's father. He exclaimed
enthusiastically, "He had never seen such a
disturbing menu, so gloomy, so horribly
terrifying. And who is the artist
who cooked this?" I pointed to Pina, who was
looking at the plates with a possessive attitude.
He approached and murmured, "May I have this
dance, ma'am or miss?" She replied
proudly, "Miss." He
whispered excitedly, "Allow me to
introduce myself." The mouse had brax
to serve you. "May I ask your
name?"
Pina replied. "He insisted." Pinar insisted, "And
what else do you think?" Pinar said
feistily. "She then granted him the waltz.
The two of them danced, looking into each other's eyes, close
together like two little birds. Tea
shook her head. "They are definitely
hopelessly in love."
Chapter 15: The party continued. I was getting
more and more tired and I couldn't wait to
go to sleep until 5:00 in the
morning.  the guests hadn't even started to leave i
surprised bury mouse and pina in the
cemetery in the clear moonlight
he was declaring his love
pina swear to me that from now on you
will cook just for me making me the
happiest rodent in ratonia she exclaimed
excitedly in land mouse how romantic you
are i've always dreamed of an
elegant and distinguished rodent like you always
dressed in black they both left in
his hearse while pinar
excitedly waved with her paw out the
window let's get married then
we'll go on our honeymoon to trade atom already
vampire land spooky
gave me a bewitching look
jeronimo why don't you take me to
transit or they say it's such a
romantically spectral place I murmured i just
remembered that I have an
urgent very urgent matter i beg you i
excused myself but I must go to the
dentist immediately right leave min
and rushed to confirm it yes uncle
jeronimo you must go quickly very quickly
you have an urgent appointment quickly
spooky /  he closed his eyes with a suspicious expression
to the dentist at 5 in the morning what is
more important than health health with
a solemn hand kiss and then I left
hailing a taxi on the fly I took refuge in
my house letting out a sigh of relief
uff finally only at that moment the
phone rang I answered here stilton geronimo
stilton was my commercial director whip
nor jeronimo the book is a success I
muttered quite confused that as
he exclaimed more and more excited if we have
achieved it I understood less and
less sorry who has achieved it he
shouted into the phone your book the
halloween book is at the top of the
best sellers list
we have to reissue we will earn a mega
million to lick our whiskers I
sigh well well a little while not ahem
I am very happy wow I would never have
imagined that a book born by
chance written so quickly could
have such an enormous success I suspect that
you too are curious to
read the book that I have written
here it is for you all yours with
a hug to the cheese of your
rodent friend  Geronimo Stilton,
that's all. If you want me to continue
making videos in which I read books
so you can listen to them,
leave it in a comment until
next time.